wayfair.com.au 2013-06-05

# Furniture Online, Outdoor Furniture, Beds, Lighting, Bar stools, Rugs – Wayfair.com.au Customer Service: General Information

## General Information

Privacy Policy This policy sets out how Wayfair Australia will handle the personal information that you may disclose to us when you use a Wayfair Australia website or other Wayfair Australia services. This policy contains information on how Wayfair Australia collects, uses, discloses and stores personal information. The policy can be broadly summed up by this statement: **Wayfair Australia will not sell or rent your information to another party and will only use your personal information for the purpose of providing the products and services you have requested from us.**

**What types of personal information will Wayfair Australia collect?**

Wayfair Australia will only collect the personal information that it needs to help you enjoy the full range of Wayfair Australia services. This means that when you use a Wayfair Australia website or other Wayfair Australia services, Wayfair Australia may collect personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address and age.

Wayfair Australia does not collect sensitive information (for example: medical history) from users of the Wayfair Australia website. 

**How Wayfair Australia collects personal information**

We collect personal information from you if you buy something from us, if you subscribe to our newsletter(s), if you sign up for an account with us and also if you enter a Wayfair Australia competition. 

We may also collect personal information, when you use a Wayfair Australia site, by using cookies, recording your IP address and other statistical methods. 

When you share personal information with us, we will use our best endeavours to store and protect it securely. We will use SSL encryption to help us with this task. 

**How we use your personal information**

In general, Wayfair Australia will only use your personal information to provide the product or service that you have requested from us. More specifically, Wayfair Australia may use your personal information to: 

  * Communicate with you to facilitate your order
  * Arrange delivery of the item(s) that you have ordered
  * Take payment for the item(s) you have purchased

Wayfair Australia may also use your personal information to assist you with product choices and to keep you informed of changes to product ranges or special offers. 

Wayfair Australia uses cookies, IP addresses and other statistical information to improve our websites, look at aggregated usage statistics, save items that are in your basket and provide other personalized features throughout your time on our sites. We will also use it to generally examine how our customers use and access our websites and services. 

Wayfair Australia will only communicate with you by email if you have provided us with your email address and consented to receive email communication from Wayfair Australia . 

The Wayfair Australia websites contains links to the sites of third parties. These third party sites are not under the control of Wayfair Australia . Please ensure that you visit the privacy policies of those third party websites to be aware of their policy on the handling of personal information. 

**Who we share your personal information with**

_Our suppliers_

We may share some of your personal information with the suppliers of the products sold on our sites. This is only done to facilitate the delivery of the product(s) you have purchased. 

_Our logistics partners_

We may share some of your personal information with our logistics partners so that they can deliver the products you buy to the address you have given us. 

_Our billing partners_

We may share some of your personal information with our billing partners in order to ensure that your payment is processed smoothly. 

_Federal or State police authorities_

We may disclose your personal information to the relevant authority when required to do so by law, in cases of fraud and where any threats are made against any of our employees, Wayfair Australia or the general public. 

_Related bodies corporate_

We may disclose personal information to our related bodies corporate. 

**How you can control your personal information**

You are entitled to gain access to personal information that Wayfair Australia holds about you. You may amend, correct or update this personal information at any time. If you would like to access any of the personal information we have about you please contact us at [service@wayfair.com.au](mailto:service@wayfair.com.au). 

If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving any of our commercial electronic messages, such as an email, sent to you by Wayfair Australia please visit the my account section. Your request to unsubscribe will be actioned promptly. 

Wayfair Australia is bound by the National Privacy Principles. Please visit Please visit [privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/) for more information. 

Security Information When you enter sensitive information (for example: your name, email address, credit card numbers) on a form on our site we encrypt that information with 128 Bit SSL encryption. 128 Bit SSL encryption is the industry standard encryption technology. The easiest way to tell if the information you're entering is secure is to look at the address bar in your browser. If the URL starts with https:// then you're on a secure page.  Terms and Conditions When you make a purchase from Wayfair Australia , or use one of the Wayfair Australia websites, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions. Refunds and replacements - You may seek a refund, replacement or store credit if products purchased on the Wayfair Australia website:

  * are, or become, faulty, through no fault of your own;
  * are not fit for the stated purpose for which you bought the product;
  * don’t match the description of the product on the Wayfair Australia website; or
  * have defects that were not obvious.

Please refer to our Returns and Damages Policy for further information. 

Copyright – all images, content and site design and their arrangement is copyright Wayfair Australia or, in the case of some of the product images and descriptions, of their original owners. You may not distribute, modify or reproduce content, images or site design without written permission from Wayfair Australia.

Liability and indemnity – Subject to applicable law, Wayfair Australia , its related bodies corporate, its employees, directors, suppliers, shareholders or partners will not be liable for any losses, damages, claims or expenses (incidental, special, exemplary, direct, indirect, consequential or other) arising from the use of our site, products purchased from our site or arising from the use of products purchased on our site.

You agree to indemnify and hold Wayfair Australia and its officers and employees harmless from any claims of any nature (including legal costs) by any third party arising out of, or in connection with, your use of the Wayfair Australia website. 

Limitation of liability – To the extent permitted by law, Wayfair Australia ’s liability for any breach of a condition or warranty is limited in the case of goods supplied by Wayfair Australia to any one of the following options:

  * the replacement of the goods or the supply of equivalent goods; 
  * the repair of the goods; 
  * the payment of the cost of replacing the goods or of acquiring equivalent goods; or
  * the payment of the cost of having the goods repaired. 

In the case of services supplied by Wayfair Australia , Wayfair Australia ’s liability is limited to one of the following at our option: 

  * the supplying of the services again; or
  * the payment of the cost of having the services supplied again. 

**Content submitted by you** – By submitting content for inclusion on our website (such as customer reviews) you grant Wayfair Australia a royalty free, worldwide and exclusive license to reproduce, distribute, modify, publish, adapt and publicly display that content. 

**Legal capacity** – By purchasing a product from a Wayfair Australia website you warrant that you are over 18 years of age and have the capacity to make a legally binding contract. 

**Information on this site** – While we make every possible effort to ensure the accuracy of the information on a Wayfair Australia site we do not provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy of that information. We may change information on this site at any time without notifying you and you agree that the use of any information is at your sole risk. Wayfair Australia does not represent that any information obtained from a Wayfair Australia website is free from viruses or any other faults or defects. 

**Availability of products** – Prices and availability of all products are subject to change without notice. Errors will be corrected as they are discovered and Wayfair Australia reserves the right to revoke any offer, correct any error, omission or inaccuracy at any time (including after an order has been placed). 

**Risk and Title** – Wayfair Australia will retain the title to the products you order until you have made payment in full for those products, but all risk in the products will pass to you upon their delivery to, or collection by, a postal or courier service. 

**Office Address** \- Our office address is Level 1, 80 Cooper Street, Surry Hills, NSW 2010, Australia. 

**Trademarks** – the Wayfair Australia logo and name are registered trademarks of Wayfair Australia . 

**Prices** \- All prices are in Australian Dollars. 

**Delivery** \- We only deliver products to Australia. 

**Variation of terms** – Wayfair Australia reserves the right to change the terms and conditions of the Wayfair Australia website without notice. Your continued use of the Wayfair Australia website constitutes your agreement to all such terms and conditions. Wayfair Australia may modify, suspend, discontinue, or expand the extent of the services provided on the Wayfair Australia website at any time. 

**Warranties** – Wayfair Australia expressly disclaims all warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including without limitation all implied warranties of merchantability, fitness of a particular purpose and non-infringement. 

**Governing law** -These terms and conditions are governed by the laws of New South Wales, Australia. 

Gift Certificate Terms and Conditions The following terms and conditions (the "Terms") apply to any electronic gift certificate originally purchased by you or someone on your behalf (the "gift certificate") through Wayfair Australia websites. Gift certificates are issued by Wayfair Australia (referred to hereinafter as either "wayfair", "we", "us" or "our"). By purchasing a gift certificate, accepting and retaining a gift certificate, or using a gift certificate, you agree to these Terms. 

  * Gift certificates are only valid in Australia. 
  * Gift certificates can only be redeemed through wayfair.com.au
  * Gift certificates cannot be used to purchase gift certificates or gift cards.
  * Gift certificates are not redeemable for cash and cannot be returned for a cash refund, except to the extent required by law.
  * Use of the gift certificate is limited to the amount of funds held on the gift certificate. The full amount of each purchase, including taxes, will be deducted from the funds held on the gift certificate, up to the total funds available on the gift certificate. Any unused balance will be placed in the recipient's gift certificate account and is not transferable. If you make a purchase and there are insufficient funds held on the gift certificate to cover that purchase, you must pay the difference by a valid credit card or debit card. To the extent permitted by law, the original expiration date will apply to any unused balance.
  * The risk of loss and title for gift certificates pass to the purchaser upon our electronic transmission to the purchaser. We are not responsible for and will not replace lost or stolen gift certificates. Protect your gift certificate as if it were cash and safeguard the gift certificate from authorized use.
  * we may provide gift certificate purchasers with information about the redemption status of gift certificates.
  * we reserves the right to change these Terms from time to time in its discretion. Such revised terms will be effective as to any gift certificates purchased after the date said revised Terms are posted to the wayfair.com.au websites.
  * Resale of a gift certificate or use for unauthorized advertising, marketing, sweepstakes or other promotional purposes is strictly prohibited. Your right to use the funds on the gift certificate is a limited right, subject to these Terms and applicable law. We are not responsible for pricing, typographical, or other errors, in any offer and reserve the right to cancel any orders resulting from such errors. 
  * If we suspect any fraud or misuse in connection with a gift certificate, we reserve the right in our discretion to suspend or terminate use of the gift certificate.
  * The consideration paid for the gift certificate, including any unredeemed balances, is the property of Wayfair Australia. 
  * We do not currently collect or maintain any personally identifiable information regarding the purchasers of the Cards. However, we reserve the right to obtain personal information about you in accordance with the privacy policy found here if such information is necessary to service the Card or respond to your inquiries or for other purposes.
  * If any one or more of the covenants, agreements, provisions or terms of these Terms shall be for any reason whatsoever held invalid, then such covenants, agreements, provisions or terms shall be deemed severable from the remaining covenants, agreements, provisions or terms of these Terms shall in no way affect the validity or enforceability of the other provisions of these Terms.
  * These Terms sets forth the entire understanding of the parties relating to the subject matter hereof, and all prior understandings, written or oral, are superseded by these Terms. All terms and conditions set forth herein are applicable to the extent permitted by law.

How can I contact wayfair.com.au?

By Phone:1300 900 675 

By Email:[service@wayfair.com.au](mailto:service@wayfair.com.au)

By Fax:02 8264 3226

By Mail: Wayfair Australia  
Wayfair  
PO Box K475  
Haymarket, NSW  1240  
Back To Top
